# Rajab Bobomuratov



### **Junior Front-end Developer**

I'm a React Front-end developer with experience in UX/UI design and knowledge of QA Manual.

I recently completed a course on JavaScript and React development, one of the main features of which was a large emphasis on self-study. There I got a base for working with JS, React, Redux/RTK, REST API, MUI, and more.

During my studies, I constantly tried to use additional technologies that were not included in the course plan.

I also worked and continue to work on the:

- · UI library, which I used for personal tasks and as the main UI library in one of the final team tasks;
- · Npm library of TS scripts, where I put specific functions or functions that I use often;
- · Telegram bot for school chat, written on the Telegraf framework;
- · A set of api functions written in Google Apps Script a pseudo-backend for working with Google Spreadsheets via REST API;
- · Pet project, which my friends are currently using and on which I am experimenting a lot, trying out application technologies and honing the skills I already have.

In team tasks, I was a team leader, setting up projects, organizing processes and communication.

During the course, I held the status of 'rs-activist' for helping other students and moderating a Ukrainian-language chat on Telegram.

During my studies, I started taking notes in notion, which turned into a mini encyclopedia that is sometimes used by close classmates or people who know about it.

I also have non-commercial / semi-commercial experience in developing scripts and tools in JS (Figma, After Effects, Studio One), Lua (Reaper DAW), AHK (Windows OS) and some other languages.

I love to experiment and am always in the process of learning something new. I am not afraid to use new approaches and change my habits if I see logic and growth for myself.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Junior UX/UI Designer

APR 2021 - JUL 2021 // unqa.agency (agency, Rivne)

Web design, corporate identity and logo design

Presentation of projects to the customer

#### **Graphic Designer**

DEC 2011 - JAN 2015 // Bureau MarT (advertising consulting agency, Rivne)

Logos design, corporate styles, outdoor advertising, printed and souvenir products

### **EDUCATION**

## React

SEP 2022 - DEC 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

React, Redux Toolkit, React API. 6 tasks, including a team task

## JavaScript/Front-end

MAR 2022 - SEP 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

Core JavaScript, TypeScript, layout, algorithms, development under the supervision of a mentor. More than 7 projects, including a team task

The course is based on self-study

I tried to use it myself: React, Redux (vanilla), Axios, Lottie animation, Web Animations API, etc. During the course, I created my own UI library and scripting library, which I used in all assignments

# JS/FE Pre-School

DEC 2021 - MAR 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

Basic skills in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Git. More than 5 independent projects

## **UX Design**

2021 // bangbangeducation

A video course on interface design

# **Basics of QA Manual**

AUG 2021 - AUG 2022 // QATestLab

A month-long course on the basics of QA manual testing

## **UX/UI** Design

2019 // WDIR

A video course on web and interface design. Everything from working with a client to the finished design

## LAST PROJECT

## **AW**

React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, SCSS modules, Vite, ESLint, Autoprefixer, Firebase, React Hook Form, React Responsive, React Router Dom, React Snowfall, Google Apps Script, Asmlib, Asm Ts Scripts

Pet Project

Single Page Application for use within a music group. The application contains a list of songs, chords, and a chat for communication. The app's functionality includes the ability to create a song list and transpose chords

The project was started at the beginning of my studies in vanilla JavaScript and later rewritten in React. Some of the functionality is in the process of being ported to React

# **More projects** →

#### Message me on Telegram

Location: Rivne, remote

+380 (97) 123 57 33 Telegram: @amelianceskymusic

E-mail: radzhab@ukr.net

GitHub: github.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com

### HARD SKILLS

React

**Phone:** 

TypeScript

JavaScript

Redux / RTK

HTML

CSS / SCSS / SCSS Modules

MUI

Webpack

Vite

Create React App

ESLint / Prettier

Git / GitHub

React Hook Form

React Router Dom

Rest API

#### **Others**

Visual Studio Code

Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

Json, Yaml, Ini

Notion, Jira, Slack

Handwrite

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Adaptability

Critical thinking

Focus on results

Friendly

Honesty Perfectionism

Self-development

Stress tolerance

## **LANGUAGES**

## **English**

A1

**Polish** 

A1

## **Ukrainian**

Native

## **HOBBIES**

I am musician. I play musical instruments and compose music

In my free time I like to write code, automate routine tasks, ride a bike